Armash Fankar

Full Stack Developer at Unico Connect LLP

armashfankar@gmail.com

Summary

I have over 11 months of experience working in web development industry. Currently, I work as full stack developer, developing websites for our clients by using Laravel, PHP, Wordpress, Shopify etc.

Previously, I have done internship at fitrangi.com, where my role was to design pages and to solve bugs.

Competencies: Laravel, PHP, eCommerce, Wordpress,

Ajax, Jquery, Networking & Security.

Experience

Full Stack Developer at Unico Connect LLP

June 2015 - Present (11 months)

Developing eCommerce, WordPress and dynamic websites.

Internship at Fitrangi.com

January 2015 - May 2015 (5 months)

Skills & Expertise

HTML

MySQL

PHP

JavaScript

Networking

SQL

CSS

Web Development

Software Development

Laravel

Shopify

WordPress

Microsoft Office

Node.js

AngularJS

Opencart

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Linux

Management

jQuery

HTML5

Databases

E-commerce

CMS

Education

A.I.KALSEKAR TECHNICAL CAMPUS

Engineer's Degree, Computer Engineering, 2012 - 2015

Grade: Distinction

Activities and Societies: Technical Workshops, Sports, Cultural Events, Technical Events

A.I.ABDUL RAZZAK KALSEKAR POLYTECHNIC

Diploma in Computer Engineering, Computer Engineering, 2009 - 2012

Grade: First Class

Activities and Societies: Workshops, Sports, Cultural Events, Tech Fests.

Abdullah Patel High School

SSC, 1999 - 2009

Activities and Societies: Science Exhibitions, Sports, Essay Writing Competitions, Drama

Interests

Travelling & Cooking

Projects

Bebajrang.com

July 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Irasoleil.com

September 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Illuminati Fabric + Frame System

October 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Variotrading.com

August 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Biguineindia.co.in Salon & Spa

September 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Frapp.in

July 2015 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, shashank sawant

Mini Project Online Certification Using Core PHP and Mysql

April 2014 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, saima haji

Intelligent Job Search Engine using PHP (Final Year Project)

May 2012 to Present

Members: Armash Fankar, nabeel hawa, Aquib kazi, Musab Jummal

Languages

English

Hindi

Volunteer Experience

EVENT ORGANISER at AIKTC

March 2016 - Present

ALGORITHM 2.0

Theme for this event was "Digital Solution for Natural and Man Made Disasters" where we have got great participations from many different colleges and found some amazing solutions which can be used to help people during disasters.

Judges for this competition was from NGOs and IT experts.

EVENT ORGANISER at AIKTC

April 2015 - Present

ALGORITHM 1.0

Algorithm 1.0 was conducted to solve social problems like Child Abuse, Child Labour and Violence against Women, Hunger etc to make people aware and to solve such serious problems exists in our society.

Many students from various colleges participated and provided their best solutions.

Courses

Engineer's Degree, Computer Engineering

A.I.KALSEKAR TECHNICAL CAMPUS

Soft Skills Training Programme

Web Development Workshops

.....

Independent Coursework

CCNP

Publications

Efficient Way Of Web Development Using Python And Flask

International Journal of Advanced Research in Computer Science (IJARCS) August 8, 2015

Authors: Armash Fankar, Musab Jummal, Aaraf Murade, Prof. P. S Lokhande, nabeel hawa

Web is the most frequently used networking aid which satisfies the requirements of all types of users; it provides a solution for any type of problem definition. While developing a web portal the appearance of web portal makes a development more critical. The good appearance of a web can easily attract more number of visitors which is a success of web portal. For designing and developing such well structured and with the good appearance of web we have to choose a proper technology. The technological needs of satisfying a good web portal can be fulfilled by "python" and "flask".

Certifications

CEH

maharashtra state board of technical education September 2012

Organizations

Unico Connect LLP

Web Developer

Unico Connect provides Website, Ecommerce and Web Application development. We create attractive, modern, and user friendly interfaces for our customers.

Programmers Club

Core Member

The group was founded with a goal of inculcating habits like teaching, learning and sharing knowledge among peers and freshmen students. The club is very much successful in achieving its goal and continues to deliver the best by its student community.

Participated in various organizing roles.

Held and tutored Mysql and Basic networking workshop.

Held and tutored web development workshop.

Organized intercollegiate web development competition.

Honors and Awards

SECOND PRIZE IN HACKATHON (Microsoft India (R&D) Pvt. Ltd)

CODENITI

March 2014

First prize in Cricket Championship

A.I.KALSEKAR TECHNICAL CAMPUS January 2014

Second prize in Cricket Championship

A.I.KALSEKAR TECHNICAL CAMPUS

January 2013

Armash Fankar

Full Stack Developer at Unico Connect LLP

armashfankar@gmail.com



Contact Armash on LinkedIn